<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Email - Y&amp;P CSS Talc 180 Day Follow Up</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>SRLG</letterhead>
    <name>Email - Y&amp;P CSS Talc 180 Day Follow Up</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Young &amp; Partners Law Firm - Talcum Powder Case Information Follow Up</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Contact.FirstName},

We hope this message finds you in high spirits. At Young &amp; Partners Law Firm, we understand the importance of this Talcum Powder case to you and your family, and wanted to check in. Childers, Schlueter &amp; Smith is working diligently to gather all the necessary material in pursuance of your case.

As you are aware, while we are navigating this process, it is paramount that we have the most current and up-to-date information for you. Can you please take a moment to give us a call at 888-427-9607 or reach out by email at clientrelations@saddlerocklegal.com to verify your contact information, including your address, phone #, email address and emergency contacts?

Making sure we have accurate and up-to-date details is essential to ensure that we can communicate with you promptly and avoid any delays in your case.

With each case being unique, there may be other details you feel are pertinent to include in your file, we ask that you please reach out to let us know about any additional information you may feel is relevant.

Should you have questions or concerns about your case, please do not hesitate to reach out. Again our number is 888-427-9607 or Childers, Schlueter &amp; Smith at 800-641-0098. Our team of legal professionals is here to provide you with the support you need.

Thank you for your trust in us. We look forward to continuing to work with you on your case.

Warm Regards,
Young &amp; Partners Law Firm and Childers, Schlueter &amp; Smith
clientrelations@saddlerocklegal.com
888-427-9607
800-641-0098</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
